你是说这个女演员
You're telling me this actress person...
是唯一一个你想要她而她不想要你的？
...is the only woman you ever wanted who didn't want you back?
天哪
Oh,my God.
这不就是你的情况吗？
Is this what it's like to be you?
你真的很喜欢她？ 你有所不知
-You're crazy about her,huh? -You have no idea.
上了台，我可以吻她、摸她
When we're on stage,I get to kiss her and touch her.
然后她跟导演回家
She goes home with the director...
我就心如刀割
...and it's like somebody's ripping out my heart.
看你这样，感觉真好
Oh,it's so great to see you feeling like this.
爸早上打电话来
Dad called this morning.
施薇亚姑姑死了
Aunt Sylvia passed away.
我们都很震惊
We were all pretty shaken up about it.
我漏听了什么？
Am I missing something?
死亡不是悲伤的事吗？某种意义上
I thought death was supposed to be sad,in a way.
施薇亚姑姑…
Well,Aunt Sylvia was...
不是一个好人
... not a nice person.
她是个残忍的糟老太婆
She was a cruel,cranky old bitch.
她死了我很难过
And I'm sorry she died.
我有没有得到娃娃屋？
Did Dad say I get the dollhouse?
你有 我得到娃娃屋了
-You get the dollhouse. -I get the dollhouse!
娃娃住的屋子，好酷
A house for dolls! That is so cool.
我小时候只有铁桶
When I was a kid,I had a barrel.
你拿铁桶当娃娃屋？
You had a barrel for a dollhouse?
不，就是一个铁桶
No,just a barrel.
你可以玩我的娃娃屋
You know what? You can play with my dollhouse.
真的？
Really?
随时欢迎
Any time you want.
我小的时候好想玩
When I was young I wanted to play with this dollhouse.
但是不行，只准看、不准碰
But no! It was to be looked at,never played with.
我奶奶也是这样告戒我
My grandmother said the same thing to me.
更多的是浴缸之类的情况
More of a bathtub-type situation.
她给过你机会
She did give you one chance.
她告诉莫妮卡，如果她能减掉20磅就能玩那个娃娃屋
She told Monica she could play with the dollhouse if she lost 20 pounds.
是的，看看现在谁的体重轻了，施薇亚姑姑
Yeah, well, look who's losing weight now, Aunt Sylvia.
本集播出：“娃娃屋”
The One With the Doll House
谢谢你请我吃饭，你不必非要陪我回来的
Thanks for lunch. You didn't have to walk me here.
不客气
That's okay. No problem.
女性内衣不会放在办公室里
You realize we don't keep the women's lingerie here.
我知道
Yes,I realize that.
夏季型录 就是这个
-Summer catalog. -That's the stuff.
瑞秋，给我范思哲（意大利时尚品牌）的发货单
Rachel,I need the Versace invoice.
你不是我的员工
You don't work for me.
乔安娜，我的朋友钱德宾
Joanna,this is my friend Chandler Bing. Joanna.
宾？很棒的姓
Bing? That's a great name.
那是盖尔语的“你的火鸡煮好了”
It's Gaelic for,"Thy turkey's done."
我走了，幸会 彼此彼此
-I'm gonna go. Nice meeting you. -You too.
他怎么样？
So what's wrong with him?
他都这样疯疯癫癫的 我都没感觉了
Nothing. He's just goofy like that. I actually hardly notice it anymore.
我是说他已婚吗？有对象吗？
I mean,is he married or involved with anyone?
不，他未婚，没有对象
He's not married or involved with anyone.
我看还是算了
Actually,you know what? Forget it.
我可以帮你问他 真的？
-I'll ask him for you,if you want. -Would you?
会不会太可悲、太饥渴 就像苏菲会做的事？
Or is it too sad and desperate,like something Sophie would do?
我在这里 我知道
-I am here. -I know that.
你们看
Look at it!
壁纸有点褪色，没关系
Wallpaper's a little faded. That's okay.
地毯有点翘起来
Carpet's a little loose.
硬木地板？
Hardwood floors?!
好漂亮喔 我知道
-It's so beautiful! -I know!
我要来玩了
So I'm here,ready to play!
我带了一堆东西来，看喔
I brought a bunch of stuff for the house,so check it out.
这是什么？
What's this?
狗狗，每栋房子都应该有狗
That's a dog. Every house should have a dog.
不能大到可以在屋顶上撒尿
Not one that can pee on the roof.
也许是因为房子盖在 辐射废料掩埋的地上
Maybe it's so big because the house was built on radioactive waste.
这是房子打喷嚏用的？
And is this in case the house sneezes?
不是，那是阁楼里的鬼
No,that's the ghost for the attic.
我不要鬼 谁都不想闹鬼
-I don't want a ghost. -Well,nobody wants a ghost.
但是这里闹鬼
But you've got one...
因为房子盖在印地安古坟场上
... because the house is sitting on an ancient lndian burial ground.
慢着，这栋房子盖在辐射废料
Wait a minute. The house was built on radioactive waste...
和印地安古坟场上？
...and an ancient lndian burial ground?
那是不可能的
That would never happen.
你太不了解美国政府了
Obviously you don't know much about the U.S. government.
我有事找你 什么事？
-I need to talk to you. -Sure. What's up?
抱歉，我是说钱德
Oh,sorry. I meant Chandler.
我知道
I know.
有事记得找我
Well,if something comes up....
恭喜你们度过尴尬期
I'm glad you guys are past that little awkward phase.
我的上司乔安娜，你一离开
My boss. Joanna. When you left...
她就问起你的事…
...she started asking questions about you....
看上眼了？
Liked what she saw?
喜欢我的表现？
Dug my action,did she?
在探听小钱钱的事？
Checking out the Chan Chan Man!
听起来…
That was...
怪怪的
...surreal.
怎样？有兴趣吗？
What do you think? Are you interested?
她还不错，蛮吸引人的，好吧
She seemed cool. Attractive. I'll do it.
谢谢你，太好了，她会爱死我
Thank you,Chandler. This is great. She's gonna love me.
恐龙出击，大家快躲进屋里！
Dinosaur attack! Quick,everybody into the house!
你知道吗？到此为止
All right,Phoebe,you know what? That's it. That's it.
我不要恐龙、鬼 和超级大狗，好吗？
No dinosaurs,no ghosts,no giant dogs,okay?
比例不对，不是维多利亚风 一点也不相衬
They're not the right size,they're not Victorian and they don't go.
好
Fine.
恐龙，我们走 没有想像力的房子不欢迎我们
Come,dinosaur. We're not welcome in the house of no imagination.
趁这个机会，我想告诉你
While we're on the subject,I have to say that dinosaurs...
恐龙不会汪汪叫
...they don't go,"ruff!"
小恐龙会
The little ones do.
“露西儿洛泰尔剧院”
凯特 早
-Hey,Kate. -Morning.
我去了你说的那家餐厅…
I went to that restaurant you talked about
美女
Hey,lovely.
来跟我聊一下
Come,talk to me for a minute.
我在那里吃饭 很好吃，我点了鱼
I ate the food. It was good. I had the fish.
我是萝伦，凯特的候补
I'm Lauren. Kate's understudy.
乔伊崔比亚尼
Joey Tribbiani.
我知道
I know.
我是你的超级影迷
I'm a big fan of yours.
什么？
What?
我以前经常翘课 好回家看“我们的日子”里的
I used to schedule my classes so I could watch Dr. Drake Ramoray...
德瑞克雷莫瑞医生
...on Days of our Lives.
少来了，真的？ 真的
-Get out of here. Really? -Absolutely.
结果他们让你掉到电梯里
But then they dropped you down that elevator shaft.
他们是把我踢掉了
They gave me the shaft,all right.
你好幽默
You're so funny.
你排完戏要做什么？
What are you doing after rehearsal?
要不要去喝一杯？
You want to get a drink?
好啊，听起来不错
Sure. A drink sounds great.
酷，待会见 好
-Cool. I'll see you then. -All right.
该演戏了，会说话的道具们
All right. It's time to act,my talking props.
如果你们想把男生浴室做得逼真
lf you wanna make the boys' bathroom realistic...
你们应该在马桶的后面放一些非常非常小的色情杂志
...you're gonna have to put some teeny,tiny porno magazines behind the toilet.
你们看，我的新娃娃屋
Look everybody! Look at my new dollhouse!
你们看
Look,look!
这是什么？
Hey,what's this?
我用溜滑梯取代楼梯，看
It's a slide instead of stairs. Look.
很有意思嘛
Very interesting,Phoebe.
这是什么？
What's this?
甘草房，家俱都可以吃
The licorice room. You can eat all the furniture.
客人来了可以睡在滑轮床上
And when guests come over,they can stay on the Tootsie Roll-away bed.
这是最酷的房子
This is the coolest house ever!
有人要跟我进芳香室吗？
Does anyone want to join me in the Aroma Room?
漂亮 我要
-All right. -I would.
喂
Hey,guys? Guys!
你们看到我的新瓷器柜了吗？
Did you see my new china cabinet?
看喔
Watch. Watch.
还有喔
And? And?
我爸的房子也会那样
Hey,my father's house does that.
怎么样？快说
How did it go? Tell me everything!
电影很好看
The movie was great...
晚餐很好吃 凉爽的纽约夜晚最宜人
...dinner was great,and there's nothing like a cool,crisp New York evening.
当然啦，我一点也不尽兴 因为乔安娜好无聊
Of course,I didn't enjoy any of that because Joanna's such a dull dud!
钱德太棒了
Chandler is fantastic!
什么？ 你知道一拍即合吧？
-What? -You know how people just click?
他来接我，我打开门 感觉一拍即合
He came by to pick me up,I opened the door and it was just like,"click!"
他有告诉你吗？
Did he tell you?
他的心肠很好吧？
Doesn't he have a good heart?
而且他好贴心 他说他会打来，要立刻转给我
And he's so sweet. He said he'd call,so put him straight through.
太好了 不要破坏气氛
-lsn't this great? -Don't spoil it.
求求你，不要走
Come on,baby,don't go. Please?
好吗？
What do you say?
是你，等一下
It's you. Just one sec.
我要接个电话
I'm going to take this call.
等我回来，希望台上会出现…
When I continue,I hope there will appear on-stage...
一种神奇的东西 在剧场称之为…
...this magical thing that in the theater we call...
入戏！
...committing to the moment!
这家伙像个卡通人物
The guy's like a cartoon.
你到底看上他哪一点？
What do you see in him,anyway?
他很聪明
He happens to be brilliant.
比你那位毛衣女O好多了
Which is more than I can say for that sweater you're dating.
我不是看上她的毛衣
I'm not interested in her sweater.
毛衣底下才重要
It's what's underneath her sweater that counts.
而且…
And besides...
你几时开始关心我跟谁交往？
...since when do you care who I'm with?
我才不关心，你希望我关心？
I don't care. Why,do you want me to care?
你希望我希望你关心吗？
Do you want me to want you to care?
你呢？
Do you?
什么？
What?
我实在很不想说 不过我们继续排吧
Okay. I'm afraid to say this,but let's pick up where we left off.
求求你，不要走 好吗？
Come on,baby,don't go. Please? What do you say?
我没有理由要留下来
I've got no reason to stay.
停！
Stop!
停！别再演了
Stop it! You must stop!
你们是烂演员
You are bad actors!
这是出烂戏
This is a terrible play!
明天早上见
I'll see you in the morning.
居然一星期后就要上演了
I can't believe we go on in a week.
没问题的
Hey,it's gonna be all right.
既然提早收工 你想去画马克杯吗？
Since we're getting off early,do you want to go paint mugs?
什么？
What?
就是我昨晚说的那个地方
At the place I told you about last night?
对了，那里可以画马克杯
Yeah,with the mug-painting.
我听得很用心
I was so listening to that.
但是我今晚想好好练戏
But you know what? I need to work on my stuff tonight.
那明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
我想是的
I guess.
这场戏怎么办？
What are we gonna do about the scene?
不知道
I don't know.
也许应该再激烈一点
Maybe if it had more heat.
怎么说？
Well,how do you mean?
艾德莉恩在寻找留下来的理由
Adrianne's looking for a reason to stay,right?
维克多不能只是亲她，他必须…
Victor can't just kiss her. He's gotta...
必须给她有力的理由
... he's gotta give her a reason.
也许他可以对她舌吻
Maybe he could slip her the tongue.
或者…
Or maybe...
他可以捉住她，把她抱起来
... maybe he could grab her and lift her up.
然后艾德莉恩用腿圈住他的腰
Then Adrianne could wrap her legs around his waist.
-她可以这样 -并且抓他的背
-She could do that.-And claw at his back.
然后她扯开他的衣服 亲吻他的胸部、肚子
Then she could rip off his shirt and kiss his chest and stomach.
他可以用牙齿脱掉她的衣服
Then he could use his teeth to undo her dress and...
然后咬她
...and bite her!
在结尾的部份，他可以占有她
Then right when the scene ends,he could take her...
用他那原始的、兽性的…
...with this raw,animal....
像这样？
Something like that?
差不多是我想的
That's pretty much what I had in mind.
现在喝酒太早了吧
It's a little early to be drinking.
我跟凯特终于有进展了
Things finally happened with Kate.
真的？太好了
You're kidding? That's great.
感觉好棒
It was so amazing.
做完爱之后…
After the lovemaking...
天哪
Oh,my.
我看着她睡觉看了好久
... I just watched her sleep for hours.
就这样吸气…
Just breathing in...
吐气
...and breathing out.
我知道她在做梦，因为…
I knew she was dreaming because...
她的眼睛一直这样
... her eyes kept going like this.
她完全误会了
I'm telling you,she's got it all wrong.
我只是说 今晚很愉快，改天再聚
All I said was,"This was fun. Let's do it again sometime.
我再打给你
I'll give you a call."
那她为什么觉得你会打给她？
I wonder why she thinks you're going to call her?
约完会都要这么说
It's what you say at the end of a date.
你就不能说 很高兴认识你，晚安？
You can't just say,"Nice to meet you. Good night?"
当着她的面？
To her face?
我很快乐
l'm so happy.
约会结束了，我站在那里
lt's the end of the date.I'm standing there...
她在等我说我会打给她
...she's waiting for me to say I'll call her...
所以我就说了，我没办法
...and it comes out. I can't help it.
我不由自主
It's a compulsion.
男人说要联络也不见得会联络
When a guy says he'll call,it doesn't mean he's going to call.
你没碰过？
This never happened to you?
他们都会打给我
Well,they always called.
你就刺激我吧
Bite me.
他有打来吗？ 没有，对不起
-Did he call? -No,sorry.
为什么？他说要打来 怎么还不打来？
Why? He said he'd call. Why hasn't he called?
也许被你的美丽、成功吓到了
Maybe he's intimidated by smart,strong,successful women.
苏菲，不要拍我的马屁
Sophie,will you please climb out of my butt.
他为什么还不打来？
Why hasn't he called,Rachel? Why?
也许他会尴尬 因为你是我的上司
Maybe he feels awkward because you're my boss.
尴尬？为什么要尴尬？
Awkward? Why should he feel awkward?
你没叫他不要打给我吧？
You didn't tell him not to call me,did you?
要是你不喜欢你朋友跟我约会
If you're uncomfortable with your friend dating me...
我们可以想办法解决
...there are always ways to fix that.
现在就打给她
Call her. Call her now!
我满手都被纸割伤了
Multiple so many paper cuts.
他为什么还不打来？ 为什么？我不懂
"Why hasn't he called,Rachel? Why,why? I don't understand!"
她很激动，她快疯了
I'm telling you,she's flipped out! She's gone crazy!
把电话拿来
Well,give me the phone then.
她觉得你不联络是我的错
She thinks it's my fault you haven't called her.
你一定要打给她
You have to call her.
总不能过了这么久才打去说
You can't call somebody after this long to say:
你或许没发现，我不喜欢你
"In case you didn't notice,I don't like you."
那就再带她出去一次
Then you'll have to take her out again.
不要，她很无聊，而且在眼角
She's really dull,and she gets this...
有一大块睫毛膏印子
...gross mascara-goop thing in the corner of her eye!
我不管
I don't care!
你再约她一次，把话说清楚
You'll take her out again and end it...
让她知道没希望
...in a way she knows it's ended.
不管有多困难 千万别说你会再联络
I don't care how hard it is. Don't tell her you'll call her again!
好
All right,fine!
但只能吃午餐 以后我自己约会
But just lunch. From now on,I get my own dates.
你不要再帮我牵线了
I don't want you setting me up again!
没问题
That's fine!
我只是说说 我知道
-That's just a lot of big talk. -I know.
我在洗澡
I'm in the shower!
失火了！失火了！
Fire! There's a fire! Fire!
我跟萝伦说了我们的事
I talked to Lauren. I told her how things were with us.
你跟马歇尔说了吗？
Did you talk to Marshall?
说什么？
About what?
我们之间的事
About what happened with us.
没有，他没有必要知道
No,there's really no reason why he should find out.
我们就别小题大作了
So let's not make a big deal out of it,okay?
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
这的确是大事
It was a big deal.
别说昨晚对你毫无意义
You can't tell me last night didn't mean something to you.
我也在，你没那么会演
I was there. You're not that good an actress.
我只是一时激情
I was just caught up in the moment.
就这样
That's all it was.
抱歉让你觉得不好过
Joey,I'm sorry you feel bad,but...
你也曾经给你睡过的人这种感受吧？
... haven't you slept with a woman and it meant more to her than to you?
嗨，凯特  嗨，萝伦
-Hi, Kate.-Hi, Lauren.
嗨，萝伦
Hi,Lauren.
嗨，猪
Hi,pig!
抱歉吓到你了
Sorry I scared you in there.
没关系
It's okay.
顺便说一下…
By the way...
我是在检查莲蓬头的功能
... I was just checking the shower massager.
我有打去公司找你
I tried to reach you at work.
发生火灾了
There's been a fire.
什么？天哪！
What? Oh,my God!
怎么了？
What happened?
我们相信起火点在这里
We believe it originated here...
就是芳香室
...in the Aroma Room.
大家都逃出来了吗？
Did everyone get out okay?
长颈鹿没事，海盗也是
The giraffe's okay,and so is the pirate.
这是什么？ 不要看
-What's this? -No,don't look!
你不会想看的
You don't want to see what's under there!
领养的狗狗！
The foster puppets!
其实没什么，就在这里 一直都在
It's not a big deal. It's right here,and it's all the time.
谢谢你这顿饭
Thanks again for lunch.
很愉快 是吧？
-This was pleasant. -lt was,wasn't it?
那里的东西很好吃 是吧？
-The food there was great. -Wasn't it?
保重
So take care.
你也是
You too.
我再打给你，改天再聚
I'll give you a call. We should do it again!
太好了，我等你
Great. I'm looking forward to it.
有留言吗？ 在苏菲桌上
-Any messages? -Sophie's desk.
你会打给她吗？
Are you gonna call her?
我很抱歉好吗？ 我软弱、可悲又抱歉
I'm sorry,okay? I'm weak and pathetic and sorry.
你去告诉她，现在就说
You are gonna tell her. You'll tell her now.
我不会打给你
I'm not gonna call you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不想打给你，却说要打给你
I'm sorry I said I was going to when I'm not.
我只是试着委婉一些，但是你没有领会到
lt's just that l was trying to be nice,and you don't deserve that.
-我想我明白了 -这跟你无关
-l see. l think.-This has nothing to do with you.
也不是瑞秋的错，是我
And this isn't Rachel's fault. It's me.
我对女人有心理障碍
I have serious problems when it comes to women.
我害怕承诺、害怕亲密
I have issues with commitment,intimacy...
害怕睫毛膏印子
... mascara goop.
真的很抱歉，但是…
I'm really sorry. It's just that...
我们之间是行不通的
...this isn't going to work out.
我没料到会有这种结局
This isn't how I was hoping this would end...
但是我得谢谢你的诚实
... but I guess I have to appreciate your honesty.
我再打给你，改天再聚
I'll give you a call. We should do it again sometime!
贝丝，我想说的是
Anyway,Beth,what I'm saying is...
我跟你回家之前 应该先考虑你的心情
... I should have considered your feelings before I went home with you.
我最近体会到你的感觉
I've recently learned what it's like to be on your side...
我很抱歉
...and I'm sorry.
你可以原谅我吗？
Do you think you can forgive me?
太好了，谢谢
Great. Thanks.
珍妮佛？
Hello,Jennifer?
罗里欧太太，珍妮佛在吗？
Hi,Mrs. Laurio. Is Jennifer there?
她不在？
She's not home,huh?
事实上，我也需要找你谈谈
Actually I kind of need to talk to you too.